[
  {
    "question":"ハイシー",
    "correct":"アスコルビン",
    "choice1":"トコフェロール",
    "choice2":"リボフラビン",
    "choice3":"ナイアシン",
    "choice4":"アスコルビン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ニチファーゲン",
    "correct":"グリチルリチングリシンメチオニン",
    "choice1":"ミチグリニドカルシウムボグリボース",
    "choice2":"エドキサバントシル",
    "choice3":"ミラベグロン",
    "choice4":"グリチルリチングリシンメチオニン"
  },
  {
    "question":"スイニー",
    "correct":"アナグリプチン",
    "choice1":"シタグリプチン",
    "choice2":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice3":"アナグリプチン",
    "choice4":"アログリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"タケキャブ",
    "correct":"ボノプラザンフマル",
    "choice1":"トホグリフロジン",
    "choice2":"ペマフィブラート",
    "choice3":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice4":"ボノプラザンフマル"
  },
  {
    "question":"トランサミン",
    "correct":"トラネキサム",
    "choice1":"エプチアミン",
    "choice2":"エプタコグ",
    "choice3":"トラネキサム",
    "choice4":"εアミノカプロン酸"
  },
  {
    "question":"シナール",
    "correct":"アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム",
    "choice1":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice2":"スボレキサント",
    "choice3":"アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choice4":"アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"ビフロキシン",
    "correct":"リボフラビンピリドキシン",
    "choice1":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice2":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice3":"シタグリプチンリン",
    "choice4":"リボフラビンピリドキシン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ユベラ",
    "correct":"トコフェロールエステル",
    "choice1":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice2":"プラスグレル",
    "choice3":"エロビキシバット",
    "choice4":"トコフェロールエステル"
  },
  {
    "question":"ノイロトロピン",
    "correct":"ワクシニアウイルス",
    "choice1":"ペマフィブラート",
    "choice2":"イプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choice3":"ビベグロン",
    "choice4":"ワクシニアウイルス"
  },
  {
    "question":"スーグラ",
    "correct":"イプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choice1":"スボレキサント",
    "choice2":"イプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choice3":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice4":"テネリグリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"デベルザ",
    "correct":"トホグリフロジン",
    "choice1":"ダパグリフロジン",
    "choice2":"トホグリフロジン",
    "choice3":"カナグリフロジン",
    "choice4":"エンパグリフロジン"
  },
  {
    "question":"セルベックス",
    "correct":"テプレノン",
    "choice1":"ミソプロストール",
    "choice2":"テプレノン",
    "choice3":"スクラルファート",
    "choice4":"レバミピド"
  },
  {
    "question":"トピロリック",
    "correct":"トピロキソスタット",
    "choice1":"アロプリノール",
    "choice2":"ベンズブロマロン",
    "choice3":"トピロキソスタット",
    "choice4":"フェブキソスタット"
  },
  {
    "question":"ジャヌビア",
    "correct":"シタグリプチンリン",
    "choice1":"トラネキサム",
    "choice2":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice3":"シタグリプチンリン",
    "choice4":"デキストロメトルファンクレゾールスルホンカリウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"アローゼン",
    "correct":"センナセンナ",
    "choice1":"センナセンナ",
    "choice2":"デキストロメトルファンクレゾールスルホンカリウム",
    "choice3":"アセトアミノフェン",
    "choice4":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール"
  },
  {
    "question":"リクシアナ",
    "correct":"エドキサバントシル",
    "choice1":"エドキサバントシル",
    "choice2":"センナセンナ",
    "choice3":"プロカテロール",
    "choice4":"エンパグリフロジンリナグリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"トラディアンス",
    "correct":"エンパグリフロジンリナグリプチン",
    "choice1":"アコチアミド",
    "choice2":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice3":"エンパグリフロジンリナグリプチン",
    "choice4":"アトバコン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ベルソムラ",
    "correct":"スボレキサント",
    "choice1":"レンボレキサント",
    "choice2":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice3":"スボレキサント",
    "choice4":"トリアゾラム"
  },
  {
    "question":"スージャヌ",
    "correct":"シタグリプチンリンイプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choice1":"シタグリプチンリンイプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choice2":"アトバコン",
    "choice3":"リボフラビンピリドキシン",
    "choice4":"エチゾラム"
  },
  {
    "question":"ツイミーグ",
    "correct":"イメグリミン",
    "choice1":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice2":"アテノロール",
    "choice3":"クエンナトリウム",
    "choice4":"イメグリミン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ワイテンス",
    "correct":"グアナベンズ",
    "choice1":"アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choice2":"ペルフェナジンマレイン",
    "choice3":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice4":"グアナベンズ"
  },
  {
    "question":"グーフィス",
    "correct":"エロビキシバット",
    "choice1":"スボレキサント",
    "choice2":"エロビキシバット",
    "choice3":"アスコルビン",
    "choice4":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ツートラム",
    "correct":"トラマドール",
    "choice1":"テプレノン",
    "choice2":"アモキシシリン",
    "choice3":"トラマドール",
    "choice4":"アログリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ペリアクチン",
    "correct":"シプロヘプタジン",
    "choice1":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice2":"スボレキサント",
    "choice3":"エドキサバントシル",
    "choice4":"シプロヘプタジン"
  },
  {
    "question":"フォシーガ",
    "correct":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice1":"ピリン",
    "choice2":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice3":"デキストロメトルファン",
    "choice4":"アナグリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ベタニス",
    "correct":"ミラベグロン",
    "choice1":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice2":"アスパラギンカルシウム",
    "choice3":"アセトアミノフェン",
    "choice4":"ミラベグロン"
  },
  {
    "question":"パルモディア",
    "correct":"ペマフィブラート",
    "choice1":"ペマフィブラート",
    "choice2":"シタグリプチンリン",
    "choice3":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice4":"リボフラビンピリドキシン"
  },
  {
    "question":"チラーヂン",
    "correct":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice1":"レンボレキサント",
    "choice2":"スボレキサント",
    "choice3":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice4":"プロカテロール"
  },
  {
    "question":"グルベス",
    "correct":"ミチグリニド",
    "choice1":"ミチグリニド",
    "choice2":"ナトリウムカリウムマグネシウム",
    "choice3":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice4":"アスピリンランソプラゾール"
  },
  {
    "question":"フェロミア",
    "correct":"クエンナトリウム",
    "choice1":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice2":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice3":"トピロキソスタット",
    "choice4":"クエンナトリウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"メプチンミニ",
    "correct":"プロカテロール",
    "choice1":"アテノロール",
    "choice2":"ミラベグロン",
    "choice3":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice4":"プロカテロール"
  },
  {
    "question":"ピーゼットシー",
    "correct":"ペルフェナジンマレイン",
    "choice1":"ミラベグロン",
    "choice2":"トラネキサム",
    "choice3":"ペルフェナジンマレイン",
    "choice4":"リボフラビンピリドキシン"
  },
  {
    "question":"パーキネス",
    "correct":"トリヘキシフェニジル",
    "choice1":"トリヘキシフェニジル",
    "choice2":"シプロヘプタジン",
    "choice3":"デキストロメトルファン",
    "choice4":"ペルフェナジンマレイン"
  },
  {
    "question":"ベオーバ",
    "correct":"ビベグロン",
    "choice1":"アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choice2":"ビベグロン",
    "choice3":"バダデュスタット",
    "choice4":"アトバコン"
  },
  {
    "question":"サワシリン",
    "correct":"アモキシシリン",
    "choice1":"トホグリフロジン",
    "choice2":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice3":"アモキシシリン",
    "choice4":"アスパラギンカルシウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"メジコン",
    "correct":"デキストロメトルファン",
    "choice1":"ミロガバリンベシル",
    "choice2":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice3":"ペルフェナジンマレイン",
    "choice4":"デキストロメトルファン"
  },
  {
    "question":"エンレスト",
    "correct":"サクビトリルバルサルタンナトリウム",
    "choice1":"アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム",
    "choice2":"アテノロール",
    "choice3":"グリチルリチングリシンメチオニン",
    "choice4":"サクビトリルバルサルタンナトリウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"ジャディアンス",
    "correct":"エンパグリフロジン",
    "choice1":"エンパグリフロジン",
    "choice2":"トホグリフロジン",
    "choice3":"ダパグリフロジン",
    "choice4":"カナグリフロジン"
  },
  {
    "question":"リオベル",
    "correct":"アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choice1":"プレドニゾロン",
    "choice2":"アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choice3":"アスパラギンカルシウム",
    "choice4":"シプロヘプタジン"
  },
  {
    "question":"テネリア",
    "correct":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice1":"ナトリウムカリウムマグネシウム",
    "choice2":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice3":"アスパラギンカルシウム",
    "choice4":"アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"タケルダ",
    "correct":"アスピリンランソプラゾール",
    "choice1":"ワクシニアウイルス",
    "choice2":"リナグリプチン",
    "choice3":"アスピリンランソプラゾール",
    "choice4":"アスパラギンカルシウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"デパス",
    "correct":"エチゾラム",
    "choice1":"アコチアミド",
    "choice2":"エチゾラム",
    "choice3":"ワクシニアウイルス",
    "choice4":"エンザルタミド"
  },
  {
    "question":"ハルシオン",
    "correct":"トリアゾラム",
    "choice1":"ペマフィブラート",
    "choice2":"ナトリウムカリウムマグネシウム",
    "choice3":"トリアゾラム",
    "choice4":"クエンナトリウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"レキソタン",
    "correct":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice1":"ナトリウムカリウムマグネシウム",
    "choice2":"トコフェロールエステル",
    "choice3":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice4":"ブロマゼパム"
  },
  {
    "question":"プレドニゾロン",
    "correct":"プレドニゾロン",
    "choice1":"シプロヘプタジン",
    "choice2":"トコフェロールエステル",
    "choice3":"プレドニゾロン",
    "choice4":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン"
  },
  {
    "question":"イクスタンジ",
    "correct":"エンザルタミド",
    "choice1":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice2":"リボフラビンピリドキシン",
    "choice3":"エンザルタミド",
    "choice4":"レボチロキシンナトリウム"
  },
  {
    "question":"サムチレール",
    "correct":"アトバコン",
    "choice1":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice2":"エドキサバントシル",
    "choice3":"ビベグロン",
    "choice4":"アトバコン"
  },
  {
    "question":"バフセオ",
    "correct":"バダデュスタット",
    "choice1":"テプレノン",
    "choice2":"センナセンナ",
    "choice3":"クエンナトリウム",
    "choice4":"バダデュスタット"
  },
  {
    "question":"ジレニア",
    "correct":"フィンゴリモド",
    "choice1":"デキストロメトルファン",
    "choice2":"アログリプチン",
    "choice3":"ミチグリニドカルシウムボグリボース",
    "choice4":"フィンゴリモド"
  },
  {
    "question":"タリージェ",
    "correct":"ミロガバリンベシル",
    "choice1":"スボレキサント",
    "choice2":"ミロガバリンベシル",
    "choice3":"バダデュスタット",
    "choice4":"アテノロール"
  },
  {
    "question":"ネシーナ",
    "correct":"アログリプチン",
    "choice1":"テネリグリプチン",
    "choice2":"アログリプチン",
    "choice3":"ビルダグリプチン",
    "choice4":"シタグリプチン"
  },
  {
    "question":"トラゼンタ",
    "correct":"リナグリプチン",
    "choice1":"サクビトリルバルサルタンナトリウム",
    "choice2":"リナグリプチン",
    "choice3":"ブロマゼパム",
    "choice4":"シタグリプチンリンイプラグリフロジンプロリン"
  },
  {
    "question":"デエビゴ",
    "correct":"レンボレキサント",
    "choice1":"テプレノン",
    "choice2":"アスピリンランソプラゾール",
    "choice3":"レンボレキサント",
    "choice4":"トラネキサム"
  },
  {
    "question":"マイスリー",
    "correct":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice1":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice2":"トリアゾラム",
    "choice3":"エスタゾラム",
    "choice4":"ブロチゾラム"
  },
  {
    "question":"セレスタミン",
    "correct":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice1":"ベタメタゾンクロルフェニラミンマレイン",
    "choice2":"ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choice3":"ボノプラザンフマル",
    "choice4":"ミラベグロン"
  },
  {
    "question":"テノーミン",
    "correct":"アテノロール",
    "choice1":"アテノロール",
    "choice2":"クエンナトリウム",
    "choice3":"ピリン",
    "choice4":"ボノプラザンフマル"
  },
  {
    "question":"カロナール",
    "correct":"アセトアミノフェン",
    "choice1":"ロキソプロフェン",
    "choice2":"アセトアミノフェン",
    "choice3":"イブプロフェン",
    "choice4":"セレコキシブ"
  },
  {
    "question":"エフィエント",
    "correct":"プラスグレル",
    "choice1":"グアナベンズ",
    "choice2":"レボチロキシンナトリウム",
    "choice3":"プラスグレル",
    "choice4":"アセトアミノフェン"
  },
  {
    "question":"アコファイド",
    "correct":"アコチアミド",
    "choice1":"アコチアミド",
    "choice2":"リナグリプチン",
    "choice3":"ゾルピデム",
    "choice4":"アスコルビン"
  }
]